<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Marg Darshika</string>

    //Floods

    <string name="pastaIngredients">
Stay informed about flood risks in your area and follow evacuation orders promptly.
\n2.Move to higher ground if flooding is imminent or if authorities advise evacuation.
\n3.Keep emergency supplies, including food, water, medications, and important documents, in a waterproof container.
\n4.Turn off utilities like electricity and gas if instructed to do so to prevent hazards.
\n5.Listen to local authorities and weather reports for updates and instructions.</string>
    <string name="pastaDesc">Don\'t walk or drive through floodwaters, as they can be deeper or faster-moving than they appear.
\n2.Avoid contact with floodwater, which may contain contaminants, debris, or hidden hazards.
\n3.Don\'t stay in low-lying areas or near rivers, streams, or coastal areas during flood warnings.
\n4.Avoid using electrical appliances or equipment in flooded areas until it\'s safe to do so.
\n5.Don\'t ignore evacuation orders or warnings from emergency officials.</string>

    //Cyclone

    <string name="maggiIngredients">
\n1.Stay informed about cyclone warnings and updates from official sources.
\n2.Secure loose objects and outdoor furniture to prevent them from becoming projectiles.
\n3.Keep emergency supplies like food, water, medications, and first aid kits handy.
\n4.Reinforce doors and windows or use storm shutters to protect your home.
\n5.Evacuate to a safe location if authorities advise you to do so.    </string>

    <string name="maggieDesc">1.Don\'t ignore evacuation orders; take them seriously for your safety.
\n2.Don\'t go near windows during the cyclone as flying debris could cause injury.
\n3.Avoid using candles or open flames if the power goes out; use flashlights instead.
\n4.Don\'t drive through flooded areas; the water may be deeper than it appears.
\n5.Don\'t spread rumors or misinformation; rely on official channels for information.</string>

    //Eathquakes

    <string name="cakeIngredients">
\n1.Drop, cover, and hold on during an earthquake to protect yourself from falling objects.
\n2.Identify safe spots in each room, such as under sturdy tables or desks, and practice earthquake drills.
\n3.Secure heavy furniture and appliances to prevent them from tipping over.
\n4.Keep emergency supplies like water, food, flashlight, and first aid kit in an accessible place.
    </string>

    <string name="cakeDesc">1.Don\'t use elevators during or immediately after an earthquake; use stairs instead.
\n2.Avoid standing near windows, mirrors, or tall furniture that could topple over.
\n3.Don\'t light matches or candles if there\'s a gas leak; use a flashlight to inspect for damage.
\n4.Don\'t rush outside during shaking; wait until it\'s safe and then exit carefully, watching for debris.
</string>

    //Heat Waves

    <string name="pancakeIngredients">1.Stay hydrated by drinking plenty of water throughout the day.
\n2.Wear lightweight, light-colored, loose-fitting clothing to stay cool.
\n3.Stay indoors in air-conditioned or well-ventilated spaces during the hottest part of the day.
\4.nUse fans or air conditioning to lower indoor temperatures if possible.
\n5.Take cool showers or baths to reduce body heat.</string>
    <string name="pancakeDesc">1.Don\'t leave pets or children in parked vehicles, even for a short time.
\n2.Avoid strenuous outdoor activities during peak heat hours (usually midday to late afternoon).
\n3.Don\'t consume alcohol or caffeine excessively, as they can dehydrate your body.
\n4.Don\'t rely solely on fans if the temperature is extremely high; use air conditioning if available.
\n5.Don\'t ignore signs of heat-related illness such as heat exhaustion or heatstroke; seek medical help if needed.</string>

    //Cold Waves

    <string name="pizzaIngredients">1.Dress in layers to stay warm, including a hat, gloves, scarf, and insulated clothing.
\n2.Keep indoor spaces heated and well-insulated to maintain a comfortable temperature.
\n3.Use heating devices safely, following manufacturer instructions and keeping them away from flammable materials.
\n4.Stay indoors during extreme cold, especially if you have health conditions that may be aggravated by cold weather.
\n5.Check on elderly or vulnerable neighbors to ensure they have adequate heating and supplies.</string>

    <string name="pizzaDesc">1.Avoid using open flames indoors for heat due to carbon monoxide risks.
\n2.Dress warmly and protect yourself from prolonged cold exposure.
\n3.Recognize signs of hypothermia and seek medical help if needed.
\n4.Keep pets indoors or provide adequate shelter during extreme cold.
\n5.Be cautious of icy conditions on roads and sidewalks when traveling.</string>

    //Thunderstrom

    <string name="burgerIngredients">1.Seek shelter indoors or in a sturdy building during a thunderstorm.
\n2.Stay away from tall objects, open fields, and water bodies.
\n3.Unplug electrical devices to prevent damage from lightning strikes.
\n4.Have an emergency kit with essentials like flashlights and first aid supplies.
\n5.Monitor weather updates and follow safety guidelines from authorities.</string>
    <string name="burgerDesc">1.Don\'t use wired electronic devices or landline phones during a thunderstorm.
\n2.Avoid taking a bath or shower or using plumbing fixtures connected to pipes.
\n3.Don\'t seek shelter under trees or in isolated structures.
\n4.Avoid swimming or boating during thunderstorms.
\n5.Don\'t touch metal objects or surfaces that conduct electricity.</string>

    //fries

    <string name="friesIngredients">1.Stay alert and monitor weather conditions, especially during heavy rainfall.
\n2.Evacuate immediately if authorities issue a landslide warning or if you notice signs of slope instability.
\n3.Create barriers using sandbags or other materials to divert debris away from structures.
\n4.Maintain proper drainage around your property to reduce water buildup on slopes.
\n5.Seek higher ground if you suspect a landslide is imminent.</string>
    <string name="friesDesc">1.Don\'t build structures in areas prone to landslides or on steep slopes without proper reinforcement.
\n2.Avoid walking or driving near steep slopes during heavy rain or after prolonged rainfall.
\n3.Don\'t dump waste or debris on hillsides or near cliff edges.
\n4.Avoid modifying natural drainage patterns without expert guidance.
\n5.Don\'t ignore warning signs such as cracking soil, tilting trees, or sudden changes in water flow patterns.



</string>

</resources>